Contact

saadsharieff@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/saad-sharieff-dev (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Management
JavaScript
Customer Service

Languages

English

Saad Sharieff

Associate Software Engineer at UniGroup

Fenton, Missouri

Summary

Experienced Information Technologist with a demonstrated history of working in the transportation/trucking/railroad industry. Skilled in Web development, Nonprofit Organizations, Microsoft systems, Management, and Leadership. Strong information technology professional with a Bachelor's Degree focused in Management Information Systems, General from the University of Missouri-Saint Louis.

Experience

UniGroup

1 year 6 months

Associate Software Engineer November 2019 - Present (5 months)

Fenton, Missouri

IT Technical Support

October 2018 - November 2019 (1 year 2 months)

Fenton, MO

TruQC

Project Manager

March 2018 - September 2018 (7 months)

Greater St. Louis Area

Express Scripts

Associate Business Analyst (Finance)

October 2017 - March 2018 (6 months)

Greater St. Louis Area

Scottrade

IT Analyst

July 2015 - October 2017 (2 years 4 months)

Greater St. Louis Area

Education

University of Missouri-Saint Louis
Bachelor's Degree, Management Information Systems,
General · (2014 - 2017)

University of Missouri-Saint Louis
Bachelor's Degree, English Language and Literature/Letters · (2008 - 2013)